<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<sercanto>
  <ad>
    <id>2285695311</id>
    <url><![CDATA[https://us.sercanto.com/go/2285695311?q=Senior&w=Prescott&_v=4c68fa4622e2c7c02256311f74287886LIg81m6xytB4cjvInQZ%2FAQtrbiyxVHcMk1P41pYMNo%2BALx1P%2FtSeGHPePjFlHEfQ&partner=Jobrapido&s_type=export&id_affiliation=744&utm_source=tarta.ai&utm_medium=feed&utm_campaign=tarta.ai&utm_term=Jobrapido&utm_content=202207040542]]></url>
    <title><![CDATA[Senior I.T. Network Administrator]]></title>
    <cpc><![CDATA[0.2]]></cpc>
    <description><![CDATA[Information Technology professional wanted to fill position of Senior I.T. Administrator in Windows/ Linux environment.We are an engineering oriented moderately sized state-of-the-art electronics manufacturer located in the moderate climate of beautiful Prescott, Arizona.Â&nbsp;The job opening is for an experienced, qualified and capable on-site IT/Network Administrator with programming experience.The ideal candidate will have the ability to exercise excellent judgment in a variety of situations. He/she should possess strong written and verbal communication along with organizational skills necessary to maintain a realistic balance among multiple priorities. The Senior IT/Network Administrator will have the ability to work independently and with various other staff members on projects -- from conception to completion. This individual must be able to work under pressure (at times) in a diverse environment and must handle confidential matters with discretion.Position Requirements Proven proficiency in each of the following categories:Windows Servers: 2008 - 2022Linux servers: Through latest versions of Ubuntu and CentosDesktops: Windows 7 through Windows 11Â&nbsp;Networking: DNS, DHCP, VPN, RDP, network scopes, NTP, domains, subdomains. Firm understanding of domains, forests and trees. Ability to connect to database sources,Active Directory Domain Services, FSMO, establishment of group policies and permission assignment limitations based on corporate needs.Â&nbsp;Troubleshooting: Ability to logically troubleshoot servers, desktops, laptops, DNS, DHCP, network connectivity and other devices, both onsite and remotely. Ability to resolve computer hardware and software issues, including replacement of hardware and hardware components as needed.Additional skills Programming skills: PHP 7+, java script, jQuery, MSSQL, MySQL.Cronjobs: ability to establish and schedule scripts to run without human intervention.Database Administration.General Requirements Â&nbsp;Ability to work as a team player with staff and management.This is an on-site position.Â&nbsp;Education: Â&nbsp;Minimum of B.S. in Computer Science desired. Microsoft and Linux certifications.This is an opportunity to join the high-tech production team in a company that has never had a layoff in its 30 plus years in business.The company offers a competitive compensation and benefits package. This is a full-time position.Â&nbsp;EOE. Please submit resume..Â&nbsp;]]></description>
    <date><![CDATA[2022-07-03T01:33:18Z]]></date>
    <category><![CDATA[]]></category>
    <country><![CDATA[us]]></country>
    <latitude><![CDATA[34.54002]]></latitude>
    <longitude><![CDATA[-112.4685]]></longitude>
    <cities>
      <city><![CDATA[Prescott]]></city>
    </cities>
    <company><![CDATA[radio design labs]]></company>
  </ad>
  <ad>
    <id>2285442901</id>
    <url><![CDATA[https://us.sercanto.com/go/2285442901?q=Mental&w=Troy&_v=23d35310132460514d30de1e603d3edcTUAD2d%2FLj1M7VR2D2H9KCuGKNfxqDnVpMnEHfmamSawE4Vaddgr1%2Fd%2BmHpBy5GCF&partner=Jobrapido&s_type=export&id_affiliation=744&utm_source=tarta.ai&utm_medium=feed&utm_campaign=tarta.ai&utm_term=Jobrapido&utm_content=202207040542]]></url>
    <title><![CDATA[Home Based Mental Health Therapist]]></title>
    <cpc><![CDATA[0.2]]></cpc>
    <description><![CDATA[<p> This position is eligible for up to a $10,000 signing bonus. </p> <p> Who are you? &nbsp; </p> <p>Family Resource Center of Northwest Ohio is currently seeking Outpatient &nbsp;Counselors to join our growing team. The ideal candidate will possess any combination of education, training and work experience which indicates possession of the skills, knowledge and abilities needed to perform the job requirements listed below. Bachelor's Degree with LSW or Master's Degree with LSW/LPC/LISW/LPCC.&nbsp; You will have the a bility to obtain an Ohio driver’s license, maintain auto insurance, and earn CPR/First Aid certification, background check, and fingerprinting required.&nbsp;You are&nbsp;able to regularly use various computer applications requiring multiple logins, including those for communicating internally and externally, including Microsoft Office, as well as our HRIS, EHR and other online systems, often simultaneously.&nbsp;&nbsp; </p> <p> Write your next chapter:&nbsp; </p> <p>Under direction of the Clinical Supervisor, you will provide a range of assessment and mental health/substance use counseling and therapy to children, adolescents, adults, and families; provide direct clinical treatment using methods prescribed by the program; engage primary caregiver and other key participants in change-oriented treatment by identifying and overcoming barriers to engagement. </p> <p> How you’ll make a difference in this role: </p> <p>You will develop/maintain consultative and liaison relationships with other agencies and programs in order to cultivate working relationships, ensure adequate client care, provide consultative service and/or promote the coordination and development of mental health services.&nbsp; </p> <p>You will provide crisis intervention and emergency services as needed. </p> <p>You will develop Individual Treatment Plan as negotiated with the client and provides subsequent review of the case. You will record client's progress, complete client outcome instrument, and maintain necessary records and files. </p> <p>You will maintain strengths based approach while working with clients and families to assist in the retention of dignity and the development of positive intrinsic qualities in the client; maintain fidelity to assigned program; ensure medical necessity of services. </p> <p>You will complete referrals to other agency programs or external service providers as deemed clinically appropriate. </p> <p> Who are we? </p> <p>We are a team of passionate individuals who work to provide prevention and specialized behavioral health and substance abuse services to individuals, children and families in our multi-cultural communities in order to strengthen family life and promote personal growth. We offer a nurturing environment focused on personal growth and self-care through trainings and the development of skills. Our agency is dedicated to supplying employees with the necessary skills and tools necessary to be successful in their roles. </p> <p>Our employees are offered Health Insurance, Health Savings Account (HSA), Teledoc, Dental Insurance, Vision Insurance, Life and AD&amp;D Insurance, Voluntary Life Insurance, Employee Assistance Program (EAP), PTO, Paid Holidays, and 403(b) Retirement.&nbsp; </p> <p>Family Resource Center is an Equal Opportunity Employer and a Drug Free Work Place, a policy which prohibits the use, possession, and/or distribution of medical marijuana in the workplace. We base employment on qualifications, merit, and organizational/community need. Our goal is to be a diverse workforce representative of the citizens we serve&nbsp;&nbsp; </p> <p> <br> </p> <p>We’d love to hear from you. Click “apply” to submit your resume and then learn more about us by visiting our website at&nbsp;https://www.frcohio.com/&nbsp; </p> <br> <br>]]></description>
    <date><![CDATA[2022-07-02T08:21:48Z]]></date>
    <category><![CDATA[]]></category>
    <country><![CDATA[us]]></country>
    <latitude><![CDATA[40.0395]]></latitude>
    <longitude><![CDATA[-84.20328]]></longitude>
    <cities>
      <city><![CDATA[Troy]]></city>
    </cities>
    <company><![CDATA[family resource center]]></company>
  </ad>
  <ad>
    <id>2284521226</id>
    <url><![CDATA[https://us.sercanto.com/go/2284521226?q=Filler&w=Lake+Stevens&_v=629bdfee12919f099bfca6c218663048TLydgvxZ6eZKFhTI3Jya45Cz69JhmNmzoVc%2FxBG1BKOw20BgTkEo21qwdWJa2tvR&partner=Jobrapido&s_type=export&id_affiliation=744&utm_source=tarta.ai&utm_medium=feed&utm_campaign=tarta.ai&utm_term=Jobrapido&utm_content=202207040542]]></url>
    <title><![CDATA[Order Filler - Flexible Shifts Available - Amazon]]></title>
    <cpc><![CDATA[0.2]]></cpc>
    <description><![CDATA[Job Description <br> <br>Amazon Delivery Station Warehouse Associate <br> <br>Pay rate: Up to $18.20 <br> <br>Job Overview <br> <br>You'll be part of the dedicated Amazon team at the delivery station - the last stop before we deliver smiles to customers. Our fast-paced, physical roles receive trucks full of orders, then prepare them for delivery. You'll load conveyor belts, and transport and stage deliveries to be picked up by drivers. You may even be part of the team that works with larger items, such as large screen TVs, furniture, and appliances, and be trained on how to use technology to handle these heavy bulk items. <br> <br>Duties &amp; Responsibilities <br> <br> <ul> <br> <br>Some of your duties may include: <br> <br> <ul> <li>Receive and prepare inventory for delivery </li> <li>Use technology like smartphones and handheld devices to sort, scan, and prepare orders </li> <li>View prompts on screens and follow direction for some tasks </li> <li>Build, wrap, sort, and transport pallets and packages </li> <li>Receive truck deliveries </li> </ul> <br> </ul> <br> <br> <ul> <br> <br>You'll also need to be able to: <br> <br> <ul> <li>Lift up to 49 pounds </li> <li>Stand, walk, push, pull, squat, bend, and reach during shifts </li> <li>Use carts, dollies, hand trucks, and other gear to move items around </li> <li>Go up and down stairs (where applicable) </li> <li>Work at a height of up to 40 feet on a mezzanine (where applicable) </li> </ul> <br> <br> What it's like at an Amazon Delivery Station <br> <br> <ul> <li> Safety. Your safety is important to us, so we provide protective gear. All teams share safety tips daily. </li> <li> Surroundings. You'll be working around moving machines - order pickers, stand-up forklifts, turret trucks, and mobile carts. </li> <li> Activity. Some activities may require standing in one place for long periods, walking around, or climbing stairs. </li> <li> Temperature. Even with climate controls, temperatures can vary between 60°F and 90°F in some parts of the warehouse; on hot days, temperatures can be over 90°F in the truck yard or inside trailers. </li> <li> Noise level. It can get noisy at times. We provide hearing protection if you need it. </li> <li> Dress code. Relaxed, with a few rules to follow for safety. Comfortable, closed-toe shoes are required. Depending on the role or location, Amazon provides a $110 Zappos gift code towards the purchase of shoes, in order to have you prepared for your first day on the job. </li> </ul> <br> <br> Why You'll Love this Job <br> <br> <ul> <li> Stay busy. You and your team are engaged the entire shift. </li> <li> Schedule options . Depending on where you work, schedules may include full-time (40 hours), reduced-time (30-36 hours) or part-time (20 hours or less), all with the option of working additional hours if needed. </li> <li> Shift flexibility . Work when it works for you. Shifts may include overnight, early morning, day, evening, and weekend. You can even have four-day workweeks, three-day weekends - and with Anytime Shifts, you can work as little as four hours per week. </li> <li> Anytime Pay . You can instantly cash out up to 70% of your earnings immediately after your shift (for select employee groups, within select businesses). Learn more about Anytime Pay. </li> <li> Career advancement . We have made a pledge to upskill our employees and offer a variety of free training and development programs, and we also have tuition support options for select employee groups. See where your Amazon journey can take you. </li> <li> New skills . Depending on the role and location, you'll learn how to use the latest Amazon technology - including handheld devices and robotics. </li> <li> Team environment. Work on small or large teams that support each other. </li> </ul> <br> <br> Why You'll Love Amazon <br>Many of our jobs come with great benefits - including healthcare, parental leave, ways to save for the future, and opportunities for career advancement - all in a safe and inclusive environment that's been ranked among the best workplaces in the world. Some offerings are dependent upon the role, work schedule, or location, and can include the following: <br> <br> <ul> <li>Competitive wage paid weekly, with overtime for more than 40 hours </li> <li>Healthcare (medical, dental, vision, prescription drugs) </li> <li>Medical Advice Line </li> <li>Network of Support (health &amp; well-being on and off the job) </li> <li>Adoption Assistance </li> <li>Maternity and Parental Leave </li> <li>401(k) savings plan </li> <li>Paid Time Off (PTO) </li> <li>Holiday pay opportunities </li> <li>Employee discounts </li> <li>Basic life insurance </li> <li>AD&amp;D insurance </li> <li>Company-paid Short-Term and Long-Term Disability </li> <li>On-the-job training and skills development </li> <li>Employee Assistance Program </li> </ul> <br> <br>Learn more about Amazon Benefits and Culture <br> <br>https://hiring.amazon.com/why-amazon/benefits#/ <br> <br>https://hiring.amazon.com/why-amazon/culture#/ <br> <br> Requirements: <br> <br> <ul> <li>Candidates must be 18 years or older with the ability to understand and adhere to all job requirement and safety guidelines. </li> </ul> <br> </ul> <br> <br> How To Get Started <br>You can begin by applying above. If you need help with your application or to learn more about our hiring process, you can find support here: https://hiring.amazon.com/hiring-process#/. <br> <br>If you have a disability and need an accommodation during the application and hiring process, including support for the New Hire Event, or need to initiate a request prior to starting your Day 1, please visit https://hiring.amazon.com/people-with-disabilities#/ or contact the Applicant-Candidate Accommodation Team (ACAT). You can reach us by phone at 888-435-9287, Monday through Friday, between 6 a.m. and 4 p.m. PT. <br> <br>Amazon is committed to a diverse and inclusive workplace. Amazon is an equal opportunity employer and does not discriminate on the basis of race, national origin, gender, gender identity, sexual orientation, protected veteran status, disability, age, or other legally protected status. <br> <br>PandoLogic. Category: Logistics, Keywords: Warehouse Worker]]></description>
    <date><![CDATA[2022-06-30T23:37:07Z]]></date>
    <category><![CDATA[]]></category>
    <country><![CDATA[us]]></country>
    <latitude><![CDATA[48.0151]]></latitude>
    <longitude><![CDATA[-122.06374]]></longitude>
    <cities>
      <city><![CDATA[Lake Stevens]]></city>
    </cities>
    <company><![CDATA[amazon]]></company>
  </ad>
</sercanto>